pcmbtoday.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy : PCMB Today, Books, CDs, Magzines

_**Visitors to**[ **www.mtg.in**](http://www.mtg.in/) **(redirected to pcmbtoday.com):**_

During any visit to the MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. website our server downloads the pages you wish to see along with something called a Cookie to your computer. Cookies enable a website owner to do handy things like find out whether the user has previously visited the site. This happens on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie deposited there on the previous visit. Cookies will not identify the user of a computer and can only record what areas of a site a computer has been used to visit. Anyone can set his or her computer so that cookies are not downloaded from the web site server, but most people are aware of cookies and do not block them out. If you object to MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. or anyone else, using cookies you should set your computer to block them.

_**User Information**_

MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. collects information on what pages are accessed or visited by consumers, as well as information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. uses this information for internal review, in order to improve the content of the Site and to notify consumers about updates to the Site.

MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. guarantees that if you supply your postal address and email on-line you will only be sent the information for which you provided your address but if you do not wish to receive e-mail updates from MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. in the future, or if you wish to be removed from mailing lists, please let us know by sending an e-mail at [info@mtg.in](mailto:info@mtg.in) or writing to MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd., Plot No. 99, Sector -44, Institutional Area, Gurgaon – 122003, Haryana.  Whenever you give us personal data, you are consenting to its collection and use in accordance with this privacy policy, including our use of cookies as explained below.

_**Cookies**_

Cookies are routinely used by most, if not all, E- commerce merchants, including us. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s hard drive through the Web browser program containing information about the user which enables us to track and personalize the Site to enhance your experience. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, we can provide you with storage of items in your shopping cart between visits. However, if a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our Site although we will be unable to provide our users with the personalized shopping experience we can offer using the cookie data.

_**Personal Data Collection**_

We log your Internet Protocol (IP) address in order to receive and send information from and to you over the internet. When you register on our website, register for our newsletter, make an enquiry, submit material for inclusion on our website or enter a competition, you may be asked to provide some personal data such as your name, address, email address and interests.

Bear in mind that if you include any personal data in any material you submit for inclusion on our website, it may be seen by anyone visiting this website anywhere in the world. Please do not submit any personal data that you do not want to be made public in this way, and please do not send us any personal data about anyone else without their permission.

We also automatically collect data about visitors to our website (for example on browsing patterns) by using cookies. We collect data relating to the routing, duration and time of communications (traffic data), such as records of the parts of our website you have visited, services you have used, and your location.

_**Disclosure of your personal data**_

We may pass your personal data that you provided us by filling the forms, to anyone who needs those data in order to fulfil your requests for our goods and services, or to validate any payment details you give to us. Some of these people may be located outside India.

We may pass your personal data to our group or associated companies and to our data processors.

We may also provide your personal data to businesses (which may or may not be companies in our group) and who may use the data to send you information about other products or services. However, you may opt out of your personal data being used in this way when we collect your personal data.

We may also provide your personal data to anyone who buys our business or business assets. Except as set out above, we will not disclose your personal information unless we are obliged to do so or allowed to do so by law, or where we need to do so in order to run our business (for instance where we outsource services or other people process data for us).

_**Security**_

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our customers and visitors is a priority to us. Strong precautions are taken to protect the information of the users of our Site. When users submit sensitive information via the Site, that Information is protected both online and off-line.

We do our best to provide secure transmission of the information from user’s PC to our servers. While we strive to protect all personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

When your credit card information is transmitted, we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption to ensure the security of your information. We also have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from user. All of the information of our Site’s users, including the sensitive information mentioned above, is maintained in a restricted section in our offices.

_**Disclaimer**_

MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. makes no warranties or representations of any kind concerning the accuracy or suitability of the information contained on this web site for any purpose. All such information is provided "as is" and with specific disclaimer of any warranties of merchantability, fitness for purpose, title and/or non-infringement. MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. makes no warranties or representations of any kind that the services provided by this web site will be uninterrupted, error-free or that the web site or the server that hosts the web site are free from viruses or other forms of harmful computer code. In no event shall MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd., its employees or agents be liable for any direct, indirect or consequential damages resulting from the use of this web site. This exclusion and limitation only applies to the extent permitted by law and is without prejudice to any express provisions to the contrary in any written license or subscription agreement from MTG Learning Media Pvt. Ltd. in respect of the use of any online service provided via this web site.
